YOSSI KARASIK

FULLSTACK | FRONTEND DEVELOPER

↓ 052-8666064
♠ yosikari@gmail.com
➡ www.github.com/yosikari
➡ www.linkedin.com/in/yosikari

ABOUT ME

I'm a web developer, I recently finished a full-stack boot camp (Coding Academy), and I'm looking for my first opportunity. I have worked for 8 years in electricity where I got my first glams in programming while programming controllers. I'm highly motivated and passionate, I'm a fast learner and I work well in a team and independently. I'm looking for a place that will allow me to express my skills and deepen my knowledge.

EDUCATION

Secondary Atuda - Coding education Electricity Academy

Electricity 9 points. Practical Engineer. Full-stack bootcamp.

2000 - 2012 2012 - 2014 2022-2023

EXPERTISE

Javascript | J-query | Html | CSS | SCSS React | Vue | Angular | Node.js | Express Socket.io | Redux | Vuex | NgRx | Rest API MongoDB | MySQL | Electricity and PLC

MAIN PROJECTS

Monday 2023

This project is a "pixel perfect" clone of 'monday.com' app. It was written using Node.js and MongoDB for the backend, and React in the frontend. This project contains the following features: a full login/signup including using FB, completely interactive boards, different board views, activity logs, charts, voice control, and more.

I addition I used organized SCSS to make this app responsive to any device.

Repository: https://github.com/yosikari/Anyday

Mem Ganerator 2022

Was written using Javascript, Html, and CSS, without any libraries. This app allows users to generate memes and includes the following features: upload an image or pick one from the photos catalog. Canvas editor which enables the user to add text/stickers, edit font, move the text boxes using drag and drop, and save the mem using local storage. Generated memes can be re-edited or downloaded.

Repository: https://github.com/yosikari/MemeGenerator

Email & Notes 2022

This project combines two apps - email and notes, inspired by 'Google-keep' and 'G-mail'. It was written in React without libraries and includes the following features:

e-mail - the user can send a new mail with text and images, view its mails, delete, mark, and filter them.

notes - user can create notes, update, delete, and pin them, including adding images and selecting the background color, notes can also be sent as an email.

Repository: https://github.com/yosikari/Appsus

EXPERIENCE

Regional manager

Zohar Dalia Professional L.T.D

2018-2022

Manager of the southern region at a chemical company. Responsible for over 150 company customers, managing sales and service providers. Examining supplementary equipment (dosing systems) in the field and providing a response in real time.

Mechanical electrician

Feldman ice-creams L.T.D

2016 - 2018

Maintenance electrician, responsible for the integrity of a production line in a food factory. Installs and repairs electrical apparatus and electronic components of machinery and equipment. Writing programs for Siemens and Unitronics controllers and implementing them in the machines.

Electrician

Yehuda steel L.T.D 2014-2016

Maintenance electrician, responsible for the integrity of a production line in a steel factory.

Languages: Hebrew: Fluent | English: Fluent | Russian: Very good

